Previously on the show.
上集說到
Sparky did many things to prove that General Balloon was not a coward.
沸羊羊為了證明球將軍不是膽小鬼 做了各種嘗試
In the end, he proved that General Balloon was indeed the hero
最後發現球將軍果然是當年
who led everyone out of the storm safely.
帶領大家衝出風暴的英雄
What will happen to the goats and the General next?
接下來小羊和球將軍 又會發生怎樣的故事呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Doomsday Weapon."
《奇幻天空島之 末日武器》
Wolffy?
灰太狼？
I don't want to clean anymore!
我不要再打掃了！
Look at my dark circles!
你看看我的黑眼圈
What happened?
怎麼會這樣？
I have community service, and a kid to tend to.
又做服務令，又要帶孩子
I'm completely worn out! Look!
累得我都快崩潰了，你看
Don't cry, Dad!
爸爸不哭
Wolffy, your dark circles are coming off.
灰太狼，你的黑眼圈…掉色了
No, they're spreading.
是擴散
When it comes to the final stage, it's no longer curable.
黑眼圈到了晚期就治不了了
Fine, you can stop cleaning.
那就不打掃吧
Really?
真的？
But you still have to do your community service.
但服務令必須要完成，或者...
You can help citizens get inflated.
你去給居民充氣
Inflation again!
又是幫氣球充氣
Wolffy, has my tree been inflated yet?
灰太狼，我的小樹充好了沒有啊？
Hold on.
等等
Wolffy, my house is leaking.
灰太狼，我的房子漏氣了
Wolffy, my couch is leaking.
灰太狼，我的沙發漏氣了
Wolffy, I'm leaking!
灰太狼，我漏氣了
Wolffy, is it done yet?
灰太狼，還沒好嗎？
-Wolffy!
-灰太狼
Wolffy…
灰太狼...
That's enough!
夠了！
Wolffy, why are you escaping?
灰太狼，你幹麼跑了？
Inflating others are terrible.
充氣太可怕了
Son, we must finish what we've started.
兒子，我們做事要有始有終
Go, let's go cleaning!
走，打掃去
Where else should we clean?
現在還要掃哪？
Go clean the dangerous goods warehouse.
去打掃危險物品倉庫吧
Dangerous goods warehouse?
危險物品倉庫？
Here it is.
這裡就是倉庫了
No wonder I couldn't find it. It's up in the air.
怪不得之前一直沒有找到 原來這個倉庫是在天上
This warehouse is packed with dangerous goods brought in by the storm.
這倉庫裡布滿了 被風暴捲進來的危險物品
We must be careful.
所以一定要小心
There are very scary weapons of doomsday. You must be careful when you clean.
裡面還有非常可怕的末日武器 你打掃的時候一定要注意人身安全
Doomsday weapon?
末日武器？
Don't be afraid, Willie. It's okay...
小灰灰不怕，不怕…
Dad, there are so many toys here!
爸爸，這裡有好多玩具啊
Screws, fans and glue?
螺絲、風扇、膠水？
You call these dangerous goods?
這些東西也算危險品啊？
They might be nothing to you, but they are very dangerous to us.
這些物品可能對於你來說沒什麼 可是對於我們氣球來說是相當危險的
Why don't you throw them away then?
那你們為什麼不扔掉呢？
What if they fly back? That'd be even more dangerous.
扔出去萬一飛回來就更危險了
All right.
好吧
Leave then. Let me do the cleaning.
那你趕緊回去吧 這裡我打掃就可以了
Remember to be careful.
記得注意安全
Don't worry.
我做事你就放心吧
Who cares about cleaning?
誰管你的打掃？
I must find Sirius.
我可是要找回天狼號
Sirius... where are you?
天狼號，天狼號在哪啊？
Found you!
找到了！
I missed you so much!
我想死你了！
The bottle cap is rolling away!
瓶蓋要滾出去了！
Oh, my. Run!
好可怕，快跑！
Somebody save me. I can't move.
誰來救救我，我走不動了
Gotcha!
抓住了
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
I'm all right. Thank you, Sparky.
沒事，謝謝你，沸羊羊哥哥
Thank me?
謝我？
Anyway, I'm glad you're okay. Bye. It's time to work out.
反正你沒事就好 不說了，我要去鍛煉了
Sparky is so humble even though he just saved my life.
沸羊羊哥哥救了我還這麼低調
Er...
那個…
Sparky! You dropped your armband!
沸羊羊哥哥，你的臂帶掉了
Sparky!
沸羊羊哥哥！
Luckily, it's working fine.
幸好能正常運作
Sirius, fire up!
天狼號，啟動！
Isn't that where they store the doomsday weapons?
那不就是放末日武器的地方嗎？
If I get them...
得到了末日武器…
So shiny and bright!
好耀眼的武器啊
-Hello? -You're a liar, General Balloon!
-喂？ -球將軍，你騙人
What kind of doomsday weapon is this?
這哪是什麼末日武器？
When did I lie?
我哪裡有騙你啊
Needles are lethal to us!
我們氣球最怕的就是針了
Such long needles make us go weak on our knees just by seeing it.
這麼大的針，我們光看一眼就會腿軟
Put it away.
你快把它收回去吧
What doomsday weapon?
什麼末日武器？
It can't even beat Sirius.
還沒有我的天狼號厲害呢
That's right. Sirius can become the doomsday weapon with these.
對了 有了這些天狼號就變成末日武器了
Sparky!
沸羊羊哥哥！
I'm so hungry.
好餓啊
Here you go.
給你吃
Thank you. You're so nice.
謝謝你，你人真好
-Do you still remember me? -Yes.
-你還記得我嗎？ -記得
Finally, you remember me!
你終於記起我了
I saw you in the crowd just now.
剛剛在人群裡見過你的
I have to return the armband to Sparky.
我要去還沸羊羊哥哥臂帶了
Willie!
小灰灰！
Be careful, Willie!
小灰灰，小心！
Willie...
小灰灰
Sparky saved me again!
沸羊羊哥哥又救了我
I finished upgrading Sirius!
天狼號改造完成！
I'm starving.
好餓啊
Willie, let's go home and have dinner.
小灰灰，該回去吃飯了
Willie!
小灰灰
Where did Willie go?
小灰灰去哪了呢？
I've finally finished running a lap around the island!
環島一圈終於跑完了
Sparky! I've finally caught up with you.
沸羊羊哥哥，終於追上你了
Willie?
小灰灰？
Here you go, your armband, Sparky.
沸羊羊哥哥，你的臂帶
My armbands are still here. That's not mine.
我的臂帶還在，那不是我的
Then whose is this?
那這條臂帶是誰的？
Son, time for dinner!
兒子，該回家吃飯了
Wolffy!
灰太狼
Sparky, be my guest!
沸羊羊，你就來我家做客吧
Don't worry. I'm here to help you stay warm.
別擔心，我是來給你們送溫暖的
A scarf for Wilie,
給小灰灰一條圍巾
and a sweater for Sparky.
給沸羊羊一件衣服
You'll catch a cold like this, Sparky.
沸羊羊，你這樣會著涼的
So cozy.
好舒服啊
Of course, I knitted it for my son.
當然了，那可是我親手為兒子織的
Sparky, I'll entertain you tonight.
沸羊羊，今晚我就好好地招待你
Wolffy, let Sparky go!
灰太狼，快把沸羊羊放了！
It's Tibbie...
是美羊羊
Run!
快跑！
Stop, Tibbie. It's too dangerous like this.
美羊羊快停下，這樣太危險了
Willie!
小灰灰！
Willie...
小灰灰...
Willie, my son.
小灰灰...我的兒子
Wake up!
小灰灰快醒醒啊
Oh, stop tickling me. I'm not Willie.
好癢啊…你認錯人了
Dad, I'm here. I'm okay.
爸爸，我在這裡，我沒事
Great! You scared me!
太好了，嚇死爸爸了
Willie, are you all right?
小灰灰，你沒事吧？
I'm okay.
沒事
It's you, the nice guy who gave me a watermelon.
是你，你是請我吃西瓜的大好人
You have an armband, too.
你也有臂帶
The armband you're holding... is mine.
你…你手上的臂帶是我的
You're the one who saved me!
你才是救我的人
Do you remember this?
你還記得嗎？
This is...
這是…
Leave a mark. Done!
加上一個印記，完成
From now on, I'll call you Avis.
以後你就叫小飛飛吧
It's about to rain. Let's go home!
要下大雨了，我們趕緊回家
Avis!
小飛飛！
You're Avis?
你是小飛飛？
I missed you so much!
我好想你啊
Warning! Multiple dangerous items spotted around Balloon City.
緊急通知，氣球城多處發現危險物品
All parties in state of alert!
全城進入戒備狀態！
TO BE CONTINUED 2757 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續） （距離啟航還剩2757天）